# Richard Rivas Montaño

Richard has 6 years experience, he has worked with Kanban and Scrum. Also works with Angular, jQuery, Vanilla, BackboneJS, VueJS. Making APIs With Express(Node), some of NestJS and PHP with Laravel or Wordpress. Richard leads his personal project with a small team offering web design and development.

**Location**: Calle 10 # 29 b - 21

Cali, Colombia

**Phone:** (+57) 300 891 5853 i.ricard26@gmail.com

**Linkedin** 

#### **EXPERIENCE**

#### **Globant**, Remoto— Web UI Developer

July 2021 - Present

- Collaborate in development Web Application using Angular framework for international companies.
- Work as Frontend developer focusing on Angular framework.
- Coordinate with the entire team through virtual meetings and applying Scrum artifacts throughout project.
- Use Jira software to coordinate with teammates the new user stories and defects reported by team leaders.
- Work in pair programming with teammates on large functionalities.
- Fixing multiple defects.

## Softpymes S.A.S. Cali, Colombia — Web Frontend Developer

April 2020 - July 2021

- Working with AngularJS and Angular projects.
- Collaborate to define good practices to Frontend team.
- Fixing multiple error code in multiple Front modules' software.
- Making and updating functionalities of software.
- Active participation in Kanban training.
- Reactivate old projects.
- Debugging errors in Python with a Backend supervision.

#### USALY S.A.S. Cali, Colombia — Co-founder / Personal project

Sept 2017 - Present

- Manage public relations with clients, partners and commercial relationships.
- Assistance to entrepreneur events.
- Ideation and improve digital services.
- Definition of requirements about web pages or web applications.
- Development web pages or web applications according to wireframes/mockups.
- Coordinate with designers assigned to make digital products.
- Leading and guide development practitioner related with Frontend and support web.

#### **Vectorial Studios S.A.S.** Cali, Colombia — *Ingeniero de soporte*

Sept 2017 - January 2019

- Improve Troubleshooting.
- Improve backend skills.
- Improve server administration.
- Service and support client.

## **ELEPHANTS NOIRS S.A.S.** Cali, Colombia — Director general

Sept 2016 - April 2018

- Assistance to entrepreneur events.
- Ideation and improve digital services.
- Development web pages according to wireframes/mockups.
- Beginnings of entrepreneur way

#### **SKILLS**

- Self
- -taught
- Entrepreneur
- Leadership
- User Experience
- Moral values
- Respectful
- Friendly
- Good Partner
- Empathetic
- Troubleshooting
- committed
- Collaborative
- Clear Thinker
- Focused
- Fast learner

#### **LANGUAGES**

- Spanish (Native speaker)
- English (Intermediate)

## **ALQUEMEDIA SAS.** Cali, Colombia — Frontend Developer

Sept 2016 - April 2018

- Beginnings with Angular framework.
- Making new functionalities to Angular projects.

## ASESORÍAS Y SOLUCIONES TECNOLÓGICAS SAS. Cali, Colombia — Full Stack Developer

Sept 2016 - April 2018

- Beginnings with web development.
- Focusing on UX Development.
- Learning backend and databases.

#### **EDUCATION**

#### Scrum Master Professional Certificate - SMPC - CertiProf

MARCH 2022 - MARCH 2024

Scrum fundamental focus on Scrum Master role.

## Scrum Foundation Professional Certificate (SFPC) - CertiProf

MARCH 2022

Scrum fundamental.

# English course 480 Hours. Cali, Colombia - Colombo Americano

2018

## Gerencia de empresas de Software. Cali, Colombia - Universidad Icesi

2019

# Curso JavaScript y jQuery , Cali, Colombia — Platzi

APRIL 2016 - APRIL 2017

## Fundación Centro Colombiano de Estudios Profesionales. Cali, Colombia - FCECEP

2010 - 2013

System Technologist.

## Antonio Jose Camacho IETI. Cali, Colombia - FCECEP

2003 - 2009

Industrial technical baccalaureate.